

SUMMARY

Results-focused sales and marketing executive ambitious to drive substantial revenue and profits through proactive strategies. Brings multifaceted approach involving competitor research, innovative promotional strategies and continuous optimisation to exceed expectations. Continuously seeks out opportunities in market gaps and customer trends.

SKILLS

- Territory Management
- Sales Pipeline Management
- New Business Development
- Event Planning and Execution
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- Public Speaking
- Competitor Analysis
- Client Acquisition
- Relationship Builder

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Date of birth: 09/14/91
- Nationality: Irish

REFERENCES

- Audrey Duffy, Commercial Manager, Quintessential Brands
- Søren Hove, CEO, Vera Mexicana/Good Taste Aps

HOBBIES

• Gravel cycling

Keith Norris

089 966 7486

✓ Keithnorris@gmx.com

© D

DO7 CKR7

EXPERIENCE

03/2024 - Current

Business Developer & Spirits Ambassador DrinksGenius | Dublin

- Enhance sales performance by identifying opportunities in on-trade and offtrade channels.
- Manage a distribution portfolio of fifteen premium spirits brands, along with a broad wholesale portfolio.
- Increase sales in a network of 450 direct accounts, plus through licensed wholesalers.
- Collaborate with the brand marketing team, agencies, and creators to launch sales-driving activations.
- Develop and execute innovative trade marketing strategies to increase brand visibility in a competitive market.
- Opened 100 new accounts in 2024.

07/2023 - 02/2024

Business Development Executive Quintessential Brands | Dublin

- Formulated marketing and promotional strategies to drive business revenue.
- Coordinated with vendors to complete projects according to schedule and specifications.
- Designed and oversaw marketing events for advertising, promotion and reputation development.
- Hit sales targets by seeking opportunities for operational expansion and new customer acquisition.

01/2023 - 07/2023

Brand Ambassador Jameson/Irish Distillers | Dublin

- Maximised customer engagement and satisfaction by delivering excellent customer service.
- Developed excellent working knowledge of industry trends and improvements in processes.
- Trained and mentored employees to maximise team performance.

01/2022 - 12/2022

Sales & Marketing Associate Vera Mexicana/Good Taste | Copenhagen

- Produced and sent sales and KPI reports to managers to provide overview of business health and profitability.
- Uncovered business opportunities through market and industry research and executed processes to capitalise on opportunities for increased profitability.
- Formulated marketing and promotional strategies to drive business revenue.

- Paddleboarding
- Cooking

01/2021 - 12/2021

Student Assistent (Business Development)

ConvaTec Infusion Care | Copenhagen

- Assisted marketing team with participation in larger trade show and seminar events to promote company offerings.
- Updated marketing pieces for tradeshows to help with overall preparation.
- Monitored online activity regarding patients needs relating to our products and those of our competitors.

02/2008 - 03/2020

Various Hospitality

Management Roles | Multiple Countries

- Planned employee workloads and delegated tasks strategically to meet seasonal fluctuations in demand.
- Oversaw stock control to maintain sufficient inventory levels and minimise waste.
- Used excellent problem-solving and issue-resolution strategies to rectify difficulties quickly and effectively.

EDUCATION

2023

CPH Business | Copenhagen

AP Degree: Marketing Management

- Dissertation Title: Business Strategy for Distilled Beverages
- Coursework in Marketing, Sales, Economics, Sponsorship, Entrepreneurship, Business Theory.

2009

Coláiste Chiaráin | Leixlip, KE

Leaving Certificate